this is nice if we had ten million
dollars what would we do what do you
spend on the most every month food
delivery services a breeding mix are
equated to spend money on playing golf
every week something that I love so for
myself it's about my elderly parents
tears but I take care of them meeting
Leah every day needs if you could buy
anything in the world why would you
think I'll buy my own private island I
will buy time you might get that comes
later if we had 10 million dollars what
would we do I would first say for for me
obviously it's important for our son's
education and who knows in the future we
have more kids really to think about
they're also do you get personal Phoebe
is it important to you and why you're
definitely savings are very important so
that we can plan better saving is a must
what is the first thing that comes to
your mind when I say the word retire do
whatever things that
we have been putting on boil so if I say
I was going to be tomorrow
why would be a buzz reaction I would let
you what do you think is the biggest
misconception around me timing I do hear
from some folks talk about retirement
you are saying I just like and see what
they tell us they don't do anymore so
just stop
are you ready to retire expectations are
really my bank account is not willing to
retire yes
[Music]